{
  "assessment_capability_results": {
    "metadata": {
      "organizationId": "org-stoneX",
      "organizationName": "StoneX",
      "employeeName": "Persona G_G_L_T",
      "employeeTenure": "1 year",
      "capabilityAssessmentName": "Skilled Navigator Assessment",
      "capabilityAssessmentId": "SYNTHETIC-G_G_L_T",
      "capabilityAssessmentDate": "2025-09-15"
    },
    "capabilityData": {
      "capability": "Skilled Navigator",
      "subCapabilities": [
        {
          "name": "Stakeholder Navigation",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": 1,
              "employeeQuestion": "Rank the most effective methods to assess a stakeholder's influence on the buying decision.",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_RANKING",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "Their job title",
                  "score": 4
                },
                {
                  "value": "Their tenure",
                  "score": 1
                },
                {
                  "value": "How often they attend meetings about the purchase",
                  "score": 2
                },
                {
                  "value": "Their level of engagement and internal relationship with decision making",
                  "score": 3
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "Their tenure\nHow often they attend meetings about the purchase\nTheir job title\nTheir level of engagement and internal relationship with decision making",
              "employeeScore": 2
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "employeeQuestion": "How confident are you in identifying the different stakeholders (e.g., decision-makers, customer-facing teams, influencers, senior management, etc.) involved in the decision-making process?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_SINGLE",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "Very Confident",
                  "score": 4
                },
                {
                  "value": "Confident",
                  "score": 3
                },
                {
                  "value": "Somewhat confident",
                  "score": 2
                },
                {
                  "value": "Really depends",
                  "score": 1
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "Confident",
              "employeeScore": 3
            },
            {
              "id": 3,
              "employeeQuestion": "In your view, what\u2019s the most effective way to engage two key stakeholders who have different priorities?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_SINGLE",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "Focus on identifying the decision-maker and direct efforts toward them.",
                  "score": 1
                },
                {
                  "value": "Focus primarily on ROI and product benefits.",
                  "score": 2
                },
                {
                  "value": "Wait until they are aligned internally before engaging them.",
                  "score": 0
                },
                {
                  "value": "Understand their different motivations and tailor the message accordingly.",
                  "score": 4
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "Focus primarily on ROI and product benefits.",
              "employeeScore": 2
            },
            {
              "id": 4,
              "employeeQuestion": "How actively do you map and identify key influencers in the decision-making process?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_SINGLE",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "Always",
                  "score": 4
                },
                {
                  "value": "Frequently",
                  "score": 3
                },
                {
                  "value": "From Time to Time",
                  "score": 2
                },
                {
                  "value": "Rarely",
                  "score": 1
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "Frequently",
              "employeeScore": 3
            }
          ],
          "employeeScore": 2.5
        },
        {
          "name": "Tactful Negotiator",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": 6,
              "employeeQuestion": "What best describes your influencing and negotiation style?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_SINGLE",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "Recognized as an expert collaborative negotiator.",
                  "score": 4
                },
                {
                  "value": "Demonstrates successful collaborative negotiation, achieving a \"win-win\" scenario for both parties.",
                  "score": 3
                },
                {
                  "value": "Demonstrates an understanding of basic negotiation skills, such as building trust, gaining commitment, and maintaining goodwill.",
                  "score": 2
                },
                {
                  "value": "Engages in a fair and balanced way to gain support and agreement, showing the right aptitude for becoming a strong negotiator.",
                  "score": 1
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "Demonstrates successful collaborative negotiation, achieving a \"win-win\" scenario for both parties.",
              "employeeScore": 3
            },
            {
              "id": 7,
              "employeeQuestion": "Do you have the right tools and training required for handling objections?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_SINGLE",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "Strongly Agree",
                  "score": 4
                },
                {
                  "value": "Agree",
                  "score": 3
                },
                {
                  "value": "Disagree",
                  "score": 2
                },
                {
                  "value": "Strongly Disagree",
                  "score": 1
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "Agree",
              "employeeScore": 3
            },
            {
              "id": 8,
              "employeeQuestion": "How can &lt;organization&gt; best support or enable you in becoming a stronger negotiator?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "SUBJECTIVE",
              "employeeOptions": [],
              "employeeResponse": "I have a solid approach and am working on applying it more broadly.",
              "employeeScore": null
            }
          ],
          "employeeScore": 3.0
        },
        {
          "name": "Empathetic Objection Handling",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": 5,
              "employeeQuestion": "How often do you ask clarifying questions to fully understand the root of someone\u2019s concern or objection?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_SINGLE",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "Always",
                  "score": 4
                },
                {
                  "value": "Frequently",
                  "score": 3
                },
                {
                  "value": "From Time-to-Time",
                  "score": 2
                },
                {
                  "value": "Rarely",
                  "score": 1
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "Rarely",
              "employeeScore": 1
            }
          ],
          "employeeScore": 1.0
        },
        {
          "name": "Calm and Composed",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": 9,
              "employeeQuestion": "To what extent are you expected to help maintain composure and stability during high-pressure situations in your team?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_SINGLE",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "Core to my role",
                  "score": 4
                },
                {
                  "value": "Important, but not core",
                  "score": 3
                },
                {
                  "value": "Occasionally relevant",
                  "score": 2
                },
                {
                  "value": "Not in my scope",
                  "score": 1
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "Core to my role",
              "employeeScore": 4
            },
            {
              "id": 10,
              "employeeQuestion": "How often do others look to you as a calming presence during team stress or conflict?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_SINGLE",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "Regularly",
                  "score": 4
                },
                {
                  "value": "Occasionally",
                  "score": 3
                },
                {
                  "value": "Seldom",
                  "score": 2
                },
                {
                  "value": "Not that I\u2019m aware of",
                  "score": 1
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "Regularly",
              "employeeScore": 4
            },
            {
              "id": 11,
              "employeeQuestion": "You're presenting a new process change, and a team member strongly disagrees, citing concerns about added workload. How do you typically respond?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_SINGLE",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "I acknowledge their concern and ask questions to better understand their perspective .",
                  "score": 4
                },
                {
                  "value": "I explain the rationale behind the change and reassure them of support.",
                  "score": 2
                },
                {
                  "value": "I encourage a group discussion to surface other concerns and co-create solutions.",
                  "score": 3
                },
                {
                  "value": "I move forward with the change and suggest they try it before forming a judgment.",
                  "score": 1
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "I acknowledge their concern and ask questions to better understand their perspective .",
              "employeeScore": 4
            },
            {
              "id": 12,
              "employeeQuestion": "Which of the two words would you use to describe your demeanor when under pressure?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_MULTIPLE",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "Adaptive"
                },
                {
                  "value": "Reactive"
                },
                {
                  "value": "Calm"
                },
                {
                  "value": "Decisive"
                },
                {
                  "value": "Collaborative"
                },
                {
                  "value": "Seeks Support"
                },
                {
                  "value": "Detailed"
                },
                {
                  "value": "Focused"
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "Collaborative",
              "employeeScore": null
            },
            {
              "id": 13,
              "employeeQuestion": "How frequently do you encounter high-pressure situations in your role?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_SINGLE",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "Always",
                  "score": 4
                },
                {
                  "value": "Frequently",
                  "score": 3
                },
                {
                  "value": "From Time to Time",
                  "score": 2
                },
                {
                  "value": "Rarely",
                  "score": 1
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "Always",
              "employeeScore": 4
            },
            {
              "id": 14,
              "employeeQuestion": "How would you describe yourself as a Skilled Navigator?",
              "employeeQuestionType": "OBJECTIVE_SINGLE",
              "employeeOptions": [
                {
                  "value": "Learn: Already applying the capability but requires more training, as the role is mission-critical or expected to change significantly.",
                  "score": 1
                },
                {
                  "value": "Grow: Already applying the capability at a team/function level, with an opportunity to enhance it further and apply it at the enterprise level.",
                  "score": 2
                },
                {
                  "value": "Teach: Already applying the capability at the enterprise and overall <organization> level, with the ability to coach and mentor others to create a \"movement\".",
                  "score": 4
                }
              ],
              "employeeResponse": "Teach: Already applying the capability at the enterprise and overall <organization> level, with the ability to coach and mentor others to create a \"movement\".",
              "employeeScore": 4
            }
          ],
          "employeeScore": 4.0
        }
      ],
      "overallAssessment": {
        "employeeQuestion": "",
        "employeeResponse": "",
        "managerQuestion": "",
        "managerResponse": ""
      },
      "capabilityScores": {
        "employeeScore": 3.08,
        "employeeStage": "GROW",
        "managerScore": null,
        "managerStage": null
      }
    }
  },
  "is_employee_only_assessment": true
}